## Gabriel Donadel Dall'Agnol

+5548988194934 Florianópolis, Brazil donadeldev@gmail.com

## **Software Engineer**

GitHub: gabrieldonadel LinkedIn: gabrieldonadeldallagnol

I'm an Engineer passionate about tinkering and making my ideas become reality. Throughout my career I've worked with multiple technologies using industry standards patterns and architectures, helping lead medium-sized teams. I'm also an active member of the community and often contribute to open-source projects.

## **EDUCATION**

Bachelor's degree in Information Systems, Federal University of Santa Catarina

03/2018 - Present

**SKILLS** 

Technical skills React Native, React, Typescript, GraphQL, Hasura, Redux, Detox, Jest, Javascript, Node, CI/CD,

REST API, HTML, CSS, Git

**Communication** Portuguese (Native), English (Fluent)

**WORK EXPERIENCE** 

Software Engineer 08/2021 — Present

Patio Remote

Built and maintained a react native application serving over two hundred thousand users, developing a responsive and scalable app, being responsible for the creation of multiple engineering docs, and architecting solutions. I was also responsible for developing some backend features using Node and Hasura and Firebase Cloud Functions.

Chapter Lead 01/2021 — 08/2021

Jungle Devs Florianópolis, Brazil

As Hybrid Chapter Lead my main goal was promoting productive discussions towards innovation regarding Flutter and React Native and helping the development of other members of the team.

Software Engineer 03/2020 — 08/2021

Jungle Devs Florianópolis, Brazil

Worked as one of the lead react native developers, being responsible, among other things, for mentoring of two Junior Software

Engineers, maintaining CI/CD of projects, and helping the company to grow by working on company OKRs and spreading the culture, being promoted multiple times.

Software Engineer Intern 07/2019 — 03/2020

Jungle Devs Florianópolis, Brazil

Worked in multiple React and React native projects shipping products for clients worldwide, maintaining FE AWS and Mobile deployment infrastructure in a couple of projects using terraform and Bitrise respectively. I was also responsible for an over 50% decrease in build times for E2E testing.

Front End Engineer Intern11/2018 – 07/2019PackIOTFlorianópolis, Brazil

As a Front End Engineer Intern I helped to develop products using React, Redux, HTML5, and CSS, working closely with designers and managers. I was also responsible for large performance improvements in the mobile web app, reducing load times and optimizing renders, in addition to that I also worked on backend tasks using Python and BigQuery.

Web Developer Apprentice08/2015 — 07/2016SoftplanFlorianópolis, Brazil

As a web developer apprentice in the marketing department, I had the opportunity to learn and work with PHP, SQL, HTML, JS, CSS and WordPress, creating and maintaining landing pages and developing internal systems using agile processes.

## **ACHIEVEMENTS**

Open Source contributor

TOP 100 IBM Behind The Code Marathon 2019 - 35<sup>th</sup> place out of 27000